Asta Remeikiene

Coventry 07460581590

<u>asta.rem@hotmail.com</u> LinkedIn: <u>Asta Remeikiene</u>

Personal Profile

I am a highly motivated, ambitious and career driven individual with excellent communication skills developed throughout my career to date. With a background in transportation and logistics, I have gained a passion for web development and have recently completed a Full-stack Engineer course on Codecademy and continue develop my skills in Front-end Web Development Bootcamp.

I am a quick learner and keen to utilise my skills and experience, while continue learning. I am now fully focussed on securing full-time employment as a Developer and available for an immediate start. Here is a link to my GitHub: https://github.com/AstaRem

I am passionate about continuous learning and professional growth, therefore I am keen to learn languages and frameworks needed for the job. I am ambitious and career driven.

Education and Training

Birmingham University & edX

Skills Bootcamp in Front-End Web Development & UX

2023 February - current

Codecademy 2021 September - 2022 May

Full-stack Engineer

JBC Skills Training

2020 January - February

City & Guilds Level 2 Diploma in ICT

City & Guilds Level 2 Diploma in ICT systems and Principles

Key Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Using GitHub, VS Code, Figma
- Familiar with React, Node.js, jQuery, Python, UI design, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign
- Passionate about Web design, UI and UX
- Ability to meet deadlines and follow instructions if needed
- Taking ownership of my work
- Excellent problem-solving skills
- Self-motivated and eager to learn
- Good communicator
- Work well in teams
- Multi-lingual: Fluent in English, Lithuanian & Russian
- Driving license and car owner

Employment History

Waterstones, Café W Barista, part-time 2022 December - current

Responsibilities:

- Preparing coffees and teas, hot food
- Serving customers at the front and perform back-end coffee shop duties
- Working at the till

Shell Energy Broadband Technical Adviser

2022 June-July

Responsibilities included:

- Answering inbound calls from Broadband customers
- Resolving Broadband technical issues via the phone

- Using Zendesk and other software to log and update customer data
- Focusing on first contact resolution

Industrial Temporaries Warehouse Operative 2020-2022

Responsibilities included:

- Processing returns of DVD's, blue-rays, box sets and books using an in-house system
- All aspects of Quality control
- Sorting and stacking items according to different brand requirements

CDW Ltd Inventory Coordinator 2015-2019

Responsibilities included:

- Working as part of the Inventory Control Team, resolving email requests regarding stock
- Using the in-house software system
- Resolving problems regarding booking in errors
- Filling in and running reports using Excel
- Ensuring bonded stock is kept in line with company requirements by monitoring expiry dates
- Managing the inventory of computer related goods desktops, laptops, tablets, servers, switches, kiosks, variety of cables, etc
- Checking goods onto the computerised systems and ensuring a high level of accuracy at all times

Prime Time Recruitment Warehouse Operative 2015-2015

Responsibilities included:

- Working at XPO Logistics picking and packing household items
- Quality control
- Using wearable computer (wrist scanner) and in-house software

Staffline Group Plc Industrial Operative 2014-2015

Responsibilities included:

- Working at Tesco, picking and packing wine products
- Packing and labelling groceries
- Quality control
- Using wearable computer (wrist scanner) and in-house software

Hobbies and Interests

I enjoy creative and challenging hobbies such as coding, learning surface pattern design using both hand drawing and software such as Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop. I also enjoy knitting and photography.